ED
I beg you, please.
Please, please, please, please.
please.
Good morning. - Good morning.
I'm sorry, but...
But...
It's the rainy season.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how it's going to turn out.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
The music video shooting has started.
It's started!
What is the song for this project?
What kind of song is it?
It's like a love song.
It's like a great love song.
It's a song about...
It's a song about a faint romance.
It's a little bit
A little bit sad
but it also has an element of sadness
But it's also a nostalgic love story
It's a nostalgic love story
and it's included in the music video.
I'd like to share it with you
After watching the music video
I'm going to play the song one more time
It's a little bit different.
I think you can hear it again
I think.
Hello.
Now we are
We are
Where are you?Where are you?
Alien rock-paper-scissors time
Yay!
Yeah, yeah.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom
It's like this!
But this move was sealed by the manager.
Then draw me a face. Draw me a face.
Oh, please don't draw my face.
I beg you.
Bye bye!
It will be used for sure!
We Are
One Of A Kind
I'm looking forward to working with you!
[Applause]
Thank you very much.
To be continued.
broom t just
me
Me.
Can't we get it here too?
Oh, it's so cute!
Bikkuri pang pang pang!
There's an ocean right in front of here.
Yes, that's right.
Today, just like the other day...
It was raining hard.
You mean it's supposed to rain?
It's supposed to rain?
That's right. When it's time for "Nau Neba
It rains a lot.
It's true, when it's a dark song, it's sunny.
It's the opposite.It's the other way around.
Who's the rain man?
It's really me.
It's really me
Tiny.
Tiny...
It's so tiny!
Can I move more?
Not you.
Let's go!
Good job, sir.
Excellent.
Good job.
Thank you
Cheese!
Let's go with the wind!
Yes, cheese.
Cheese.
Yes, thank you.
Hold it right there.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
It was nice to meet you.
I'm moving on.
Bye-bye.
I love you.
Arriving at the swimming pool during summer vacation
Oh my God! Summer!
Arrival at the pool!
Pool!
Haruma's muscles are sore from walking.
It's gross!
Ekiden (relay race) two days ago!
I ran 10 kilometers.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
I'll take care and get back to being a student.
I miss summer!
I'm a father of 20 years old!
I'm going home!
Bye bye!
It's been a while since I was a pro, I was a pro until elementary school.
Now I'm in and it's a little nostalgic!
The amount of information is amazing!
You could make an hour-long movie out of this dance material! This is it!
Did you understand what I just said?
Haruma!
Say something! Haruma!
And so they pledged their love to each other.
Oh, no! Isn't this a little refreshing? Hey guys!
The uniforms, the pool, the blue sky...
It was cloudy earlier.
No, it was raining.
We've been blessed with good weather, haven't we?
Yay!
It feels so good! I feel great!
I'm going to enjoy shooting!
Bye bye!
Trying to elevate the creek.
This is the only good footage we have today of a beautiful woman, so let's make sure we get it right.
Really?
They're all beautiful.
Yay!
Yeah!
You sure?
No, no, no, no!No, no, no, no!
Hey!
Let's do something.
Okay, no clothes.
Let's do the first flower.
First flower!
The first flower!
Flower number one!
Next!
Next please!
I want Amu!
Oh, my God!
Who's next?
Hey!
Yeah!
That's great!
This is a great story!
It's OK!
When they call you and you're like, "What? I was like, "What?
I was like, "What?" and they were like...
Lefilée!
What? Like that.
I like the way he makes a little face.
Yuka!
Don't make it too much.Don't make it too complicated!
It's hard, hard, hard!
I've never experienced anything like this!
I've never done it before!
So I'd like to experience it for the first time!
Woohoo!
Yuuchan!
One more time, one more time!
Yes!
Haa!
Cut it!
It's over!
Very sad scene.
Too sad!
I mean, it's like...
But please pay attention to Mewisin's
I'm sure you'll have to pay attention to Miu Issin's little bit of care.
Hey!
The wind is just right.
Aren't you cold? Are you okay?
It's not cold at all.
I really ran around earlier, so I'm super energetic.
It was fun.
Have fun when you come back.
Wow!
Here you go!
Yes!
Finished!
I miss it!
It tastes so good!
Wow! I feel good mentally!
Not at all! It melted a bit and didn't crack at all!
Ha ha!
I'm hoping for a paddle spirit!
It's like an ideal spirit!
Yay!Yeah!
Yes, cheese!
Rastog! Yes, cheese!
Yes, thank you!
Congratulations!
Thank you for watching!
And now the cut.
Cut.
OK.
You like the mountains, you like the ocean, or you're a dumplingbug.
Dumplingbugs.
Dumplingbug.
Worst.
Oh, it's a dumplingbug.
You're smiling.
Wait a minute.
I'm laughing.
Aoi, don't finish.
Aoi. Aoi. Aoi.
Hey, hey, hey. That's enough.
Aoi, I'm so sorry.
Come on, let's go again.
Oh, it's okay.
You're doing fine.
Aoi, I'm sorry.
Let's calm down for once.
I'm so sorry.
Stop opening your mouth.
Please.
I think Luno Iizuka has hit the nail on the head.
I'm really sorry.I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry about that.
But this is Sazaharara's fault.
Oh!
Aah!
Ok!
Thank you!
My muscles are a little sore.
It's in my legs.